[indistinct chatter]
[ABE]
We won something?
Yeah, we won something!
You realize that's basically
a participation trophy?
Not worth getting
that excited over.
[TAO]
Oh, shut up, Tonbo.
[AYUMI] A first-year class
has never won an award before!
All thanks to you.
It worked out
'cause you were in charge.
Ah!
I didn't do that much.
Come on, you can drop
the humble act.
Yeah, this was thanks
to Ishimori's leadership,
and all your hard work!
[ABE] To celebrate,
your favorite teacher's
gonna take the whole class
out for a meal!
[indistinct chatter]
-[YASUSHI] I'm starving!
-[YURU] I promise to study
extra hard from now on!
[UKA] It went better
than I could've hoped.
I couldn't have done it without
Miura and everyone else here.
[indistinct chatter]
That sure worked out!
Ishimori's something else,
for real!
[indistinct chatter]
[TONBO] [sighs]
That hit the spot!
[SHIRAISHI]
Yeah, he picked a good place!
-[TAO] I've got a food baby.
-[SHIRAISHI] You're fine.
-So, anyone wanna go karaoke?
-I do!
There's a place right down
the street we could go to...
But, uh...
The 5 o'clock curfew.
[TAO] I don't think we can do
anything about that.
[SHIRAISHI]
She'll get self-conscious
if we all go home.
[YASUSHI] Yeah,
but this was thanks to her.
[chuckles]
Go and enjoy yourselves!
[UKA]
That was fun, talking to them.
No, it is fun.
Not past-tense.
We'll have more.
♪
Huh?
[UKA]
Why're you here?
♪
Social battery's low.
Let's walk.
Oh...that sounds nice!
♪
We've still got a little time.
There's an arcade.
-Wanna?
-[gasps]
Yeah!
Honestly, I've always
wanted to try going to one,
but I never could.
I thought something bad
might happen if I went alone.
[chuckles]
You so crack me up!
Huh?
[UKA]
Maybe it's all in my head,
or maybe
I'm getting a big head...
but, as far as I can tell...
Miura's been changing
bit by bit lately.
With life going like this,
I can't wait to see
what wonderful things
are ahead!
[indistinct chatter]
You guys hear those
crazy rumors lately?
Is it true?
Did Kanno and Miura
start dating again?
Yeah, that's what I heard.
[MALE STUDENT 7A]
No surprise there.
-[SERINA] We're not together!
-[gasps]
[chuckles]
-Where'd that come from?
-[laughs]
At this point,
why not just date him again?
No way.
I can't.
[FEMALE STUDENT 7C]
Hey, Kanno.
Got a sec?
[gasps]
What does she want?
I'll see ya later.
Ohh.
♪
[FEMALE STUDENT 7C]
Oguni was going on and on
about how cute you are.
But that man is already
property of Asuka.
At this rate, it sounds like
they'll break up over you.
What ya gonna do?
And what do you expect me
to do about it?
I can't change what he thinks.
[FEMALE STUDENT 7D]
Not my problem.
Figure something out.
[SERINA]
Not my problem, either.
-[grunts]
-Think I'm joking?
[AYUMI]
Serina!
[panting]
[gasps]
[SERINA]
Kai.
Hm!
Look at the pretty princess,
always getting
rescued by her friends.
[scoffs] Can't imagine
what that would be like.
If those two break up,
you better watch out,
'cause I can make sure you got
no one left on your side.
[growls]
[SERINA]
Kai, wait!
I'm fine, they aren't worth it.
-Just leave 'em.
-You are obviously not fine!
-[KAI] I know you!
-[gasps]
I'm gonna go talk to Oguni.
And I'll go
let the teacher know
something's wrong!
[UKA] Of course, they know
things about each other
that I don't.
-Hey, you okay?
-Yeah.
-All good.
-What happened there, Serina?
Don't worry about
what Kai said.
He just remembered
something from junior high.
-Huh?
-[SERINA] Right.
Keeping it vague
makes people curious.
I'm curious too!
Must've been second year,
I guess?
I wasn't in your class
until third year,
so I don't know this one.
I'll explain.
For as long as I can remember,
I was one of the popular kids.
[Uka and Ayumi groaning]
Sorry, I swear
it's relevant to the story!
I have always had people
who were on my side.
[sighs]
Then all of that started
crashing down,
start of our second year.
I hear that you've been
texting with Shimizu.
[STUDENT 7B] Figured you
would know he's dating Hina.
[STUDENT 7C]
I'm sorry, he didn't tell me
anything about that!
Those girls in our class
kinda scare me.
-Cut it out!
-Hey, wait!
[SERINA]
She told you she didn't know.
[STUDENT 7A] So?
It's none of your business.
It's none of your
business either,
but here we are!
Leave her alone,
before I get mad!
-Huh?
-Oh?
[indistinct chatter]
[SERINA]
The hell?
[STUDENT 7D]
You deserve it, for butting in.
[STUDENT 7E]
Thinks she can do whatever.
[STUDENT 7F] Popular girl's
gettin' too cocky.
[STUDENT 7G] I'm sure not
getting in the middle of this.
[MALE STUDENT 7A]
Girls are scary, dude.
♪
[SERINA]
I was alone.
[TEACHER 7A]
Okay, find a partner
-and check your answers.
-[SERINA] I felt lost.
Helpless.
-[SERINA] And then?
-[thuds]
Ah? Huh?
[SERINA]
Why's Miura here?
What?
We've never spoken
to each other before.
[Kai sighs]
[Serina gasps]
[KAI]
Come on, give it, Serina.
[SERINA]
We're on first-name basis?
Your handwriting sucks.
[SERINA]
No one asked you.
I'd been scared,
but with him, I was happy.
♪
Kai's got an aura
no one wants to mess with,
which means no one wanted
to mess with me after that.
♪
-[SERINA] Need some help?
-[gasps]
No, I'm okay.
-[sighs]
-You're a real nice person.
That's not a compliment.
♪
You know, if the shoe
were on the other foot,
I might've done
the exact same thing.
This only happened
because you're not like her.
[gasps]
-[SERINA] Is that?
-A compliment.
[gasps]
[chuckles]
Then, thanks.
[STUDENT 7H]
Break's coming up.
We should do something
together as a class!
For sure!
You in, Kai?
I'll pass.
Not really my thing.
[STUDENT 7H]
Aww.
[MALE STUDENT 7B]
C'mon, man, that's cold.
♪
[SERINA]
You should go and have fun.
Like I said, can't help
if it's not my thing.
[sighs]
[SERINA]
I thought he only said that
to make me feel better.
I got the wrong idea.
But even if it was,
I wouldn't leave you behind.
[gasps]
♪
[SERINA]
Ah, sorry.
That was really sweet.
[gasps]
[wind whooshing]
♪
I'm fine.
Forever.
As long as I have Kai.
[MALE TEACHER 7A]
Miura!
He's missing today?
Not like him.
[STUDENT 7I] What'll she do
without her white knight
to save her?
You're less than shit
without him.
[panting]
♪
[gasps]
[KAI]
My B. Overslept.
[SERINA]
I was dependent on him.
I didn't realize it until then,
but I had become weak.
[crying]
To Kai, it probably seemed like
I was terrified
of being left alone.
I made him work way too hard.
[Uka sighs]
But it's fine!
I'm a whole different
person nowadays.
So, why'd you two
call it quits?
[Serina groans]
Because I legitimately sucked.
[STUDENT 7J] The only reason
a boy like Miura
would go out with you
is because
he feels sorry for you.
[SERINA]
It's not like I believed her.
But sometimes,
it's pretty much impossible
to tell what's going on
in that head of his.
Kai, I need you.
But...you don't need me.
It hurts.
I can't recall.
Why did I do...
Uh, sorry.
Well, then,
do you hate me now, Uka?
[whimpering]
[SERINA] [chuckles]
Thank goodness.
[gasps]
[UKA] A lot of things
are starting to make sense.
Up to now,
I was having
too much fun to realize.
[UKA]
Serina?
May I ask you
something personal?
Be honest.
Do you still have
feelings for Miura?
♪
[chuckles]
Of course not.
We're through.
♪
You're a bad liar, Serina.
It's okay.
Uh!
[MALE TEACHER 7A] Kanno!
Thank goodness you're safe!
-Are you hurt?
-[SERINA] Not at all.
[MALE TEACHER 7A]
Good.
You can rest assured
knowing the faculty
takes this seriously.
[SERINA] Yes.
Thank you, sir.
That's great.
Sounds like everything's
gonna work out for you!
The teachers have your back,
and you've always got Miura.
[gasps]
Oh, whatever you think
is happening,
you've got it wrong!
I'm sorry.
I didn't...
What should I do here?
I mean, you like Kai too, so...
[gasps]
We're done.
I'm not his girlfriend anymore.
-So, you--
-[UKA] I like him.
[UKA] But only in a respectful,
platonic way.
He's special to me,
but not like that.
Promise.
There's nothing
romantic going on.
Ah?
[Ayumi sighs]
[UKA]
Let's go.
[indistinct chatter]
[UKA]
I'll be okay.
I don't want her walking
on eggshells around me.
Of course, not.
We're through.
You like Kai too, so...
[SATORU] Heard you got
into a fight with Oguni.
[KAI]
It wasn't a fight.
Yeah, right, dude.
I saw you yelling
at each other.
So, what happened?
You are obviously not fine!
I know you!
[UKA] Serina's still
in love with Miura.
And he must feel the same.
[KAI]
Call me for help next time.
Serina.
♪
[UKA]
They'll be fine without me.
♪
[YASUSHI]
Yeah! Summer break, baby!
-I'm so stoked!
-We should hang out!
I can finally sleep in!
I think we should meet up
at the summer festival,
if anyone's planning to go!
[ABE]
Just make sure you come back!
Lots of kids drop out
after a long break.
[TONBO]
You in, Kai?
Huh?
He can't go anywhere
without Ishimori!
The two of them
are attached at the hip!
Kinda figured
that'd be out the window
when the school year's over.
'Cause why would
they bother hanging out
when we're on break?
You got a point there.
[UKA] I didn't have to butt in
to correct them this time.
So, you'll be hanging out
with Kanno, I guess?
Never said a thing about that.
-[TONBO] You got it good, man.
-[KAI] What does that mean?
[UKA]
Of course.
If they're hanging out,
I need to make myself scarce.
Goodbye, Miura.
I'll see you next term.
[Kai sighs]
[UKA]
I refuse to get in their way.
[indistinct chatter]
[insects chirping]
♪
[UKA]
It's sad.
I heard people say
you shouldn't fall for him,
but I did anyway.
♪
I was excited to belong.
To grow up.
But that line of thinking
was way too selfish.
What about Serina?
How much have I hurt her?
[indistinct chatter]
[gasps]
Today's the summer festival.
I bet...
they look great together.
I wanna see.
Sort of.
But I could never un-see them,
and it would break my heart.
♪
[door bell ringing]
Coming!
Oh!
Huh?
[trembling]
Why're you here?
For you, if you're
not already busy!
I'm going to the festival.
-[UKA] By myself.
-[chuckles]
I came over
'cause I wanted to ask
if you wanted to go with me!
[both giggle]
Yeah!
[UKA] I've only been
to festivals with my parents!
[AYUMI]
No way!
You mean,
I get to be your first?
[sighs]
[indistinct chatter]
[trembling]
Should we grab a bite
or play a game first?
[UKA]
Uh, I don't--
What do ya say
we try scoping it out?
-C'mon!
-Ah?
-[UKA] Hold on!
-Yeah? Something wrong?
What time did you tell Seto
you're meeting up?
[AYUMI]
What do you mean?
-We're not meeting up.
-[gasps]
[UKA]
Why not?
It's just you and me today!
We can't talk girl stuff
with a boy around.
And no judgment.
I'm not about to tell you
you've gotta confess
to Kai straight away.
I feel like you're not
in the right headspace.
But please tell me if things
are getting too hard!
-[AYUMI] So?
-[UKA] She's the best.
[UKA] I'm sure she was hoping
to come here with Seto,
but she was worried about me.
[MALE STUDENT 7B]
Whoa, what a babe!
[MALE STUDENT 7C]
Is she famous?
Wow, I've seen that girl
around here before.
That's Serina from Hachimitsu!
Glad you were able
to make it out here.
[UKA]
Wait, why isn't Miura with her?
-Hey, where's Miura?
-Dunno. Sure he's fine.
Hold up!
You mean you don't have
plans with him?
Now there's a laugh.
Kai doesn't wanna
be here with me.
-[MIHO] Why not?
-Well, why do ya think?
He's probably off
somewhere with Uka.
[MIHO]
Ishimori? No way!
[SERINA]
It's okay, let it go, Miho.
[UKA]
Serina.
This only happened because
I said Miura was special to me.
What should I do now?
Hey, Uka!
I bought us some cotton candy!
You in?
Can't do it alone!
Yeah, I'd love one!
-[SATORU] Found you!
-Huh?
Ayumi!
-[laughs]
-[gasps]
I've been lookin'
all over for you!
I told you!
Uka and I need time without
anyone else around, okay?
So, I'll join you!
Why can't I tag along, huh?
Read the room, dude!
Sorry, Uka!
Gimme a sec.
I'll be back
after I tell him off!
Satoru.
Come on.
Now, this way!
[SATORU]
Ooh, Cotton Candy!
-[SATORU] Can I have some?
-[AYUMI] Get a grip!
[AYUMI] Can you not chill out
for one minute?
[SATORU]
Uh-uh!
[indistinct chatter]
♪
[UKA]
I should leave.
I'm a third wheel.
[indistinct chatter]
This world is full
of incredible people.
People worth admiring.
People who will forever
be out of my reach.
I can appreciate their beauty,
but that's all.
If I stay away,
at least I won't hurt
anyone else.
[whimpering]
-[KAI] Ishimori!
-[gasps]
[indistinct chatter]
[UKA]
Miura, you're here?
You should be...
[indistinct chatter]
-[sighs]
-Huh?
[KAI]
Hey!
[Uka breathing heavily]
[KAI]
Please slow down!
Come on, stop!
Finally caught you.
Why did you run away?
[sniffles]
[gasps]
You're crying.
Is something wrong?
They, they're tears
of happiness.
If you happen to see them,
tell Ayumi and Satoru
I said thanks.
♪
[KAI]
Going home?
I'll take you.
[UKA]
No, it's okay.
Please let go.
I'm fine.
[KAI]
Shake me off if you want.
[gasps]
I'd rather walk alone
right now.
You're a bad liar, Ishimori.
[gasps]
[KAI] You've got
a cell phone, don't you?
Yeah.
At home.
That kinda defeats the purpose.
How am I supposed
to contact you
over summer break?
And-And why'd you say,
"See you next term?"
You didn't plan
to see me at all?
I went to invite you today,
but Ayumi beat me to the punch.
[UKA]
But why?
[KAI]
So?
You don't wanna hold my hand?
♪
Feel free to shake me off.
[sighs]
[KAI]
See?
So, can I walk you?
[UKA]
No, I can't do it.
♪
I have to go find Serina.
I'm sorry!
[panting]
[UKA]
I can't.
I can't give him up like that!
[KAI]
You're a bad liar.
[UKA]
She realized it.
Serina must've known I lied!
I'm hopeless.
At this point, I'm in too deep!
[panting]
But please tell me if things
are getting too hard!
[panting]
[UKA]
Because...
Well, why do ya think?
He's probably off
somewhere with Uka.
[UKA] If my friends have
already figured out how I feel,
they won't be able
to brush it off!
Apologies!
Excuse me!
[panting]
There you are!
Didn't expect that from you!
I'm sorry
for ditching you, Ayumi.
-Serina!
-Yeah? What's up?
I was lying.
Honestly...I...
I am in love with him!
♪
I'm... I'm sorry
for what I said before.
I'm sorry my words
made you suffer more.
But it is true, and I won't
hide those feelings from you.
♪
[chuckles]
I'm so glad that
you could tell me, Uka.
♪
I was wondering what I did
to make you lie to me.
But I guess
I'm guilty of that, too.
[chuckles]
You and I must have
something wrong with us.
Promise.
I won't hold back with you.
So, you'd better do the same.
Be loud and proud!
Both of us love Kai!
♪
[fireworks bursting]
[crying]
[UKA]
If I hadn't shown up,
they would've
worked out perfectly.
[sobbing]
I'm so glad!
Jeez, I was so worried
that you two were
gonna bottle it up...
[UKA] Even if I tried,
I couldn't stop.
I'm sorry, but I love him.
[AYUMI]
But you both said it!
[sobbing]
[fireworks bursting]